<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dub on Front Left by the Speaker</title><link>https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/tags/dub/</link><description>Recent content in dub on Front Left by the Speaker</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 07:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/tags/dub/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Women at Work</title><link>https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/radio_archive/2024_03_13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/radio_archive/2024_03_13/</guid><description>March 13, 2024 / 6-7PM / Women at work (she/her) Playing some lighter and more atmospheric tunes for the boys this Wednesday, or at least, thats the plan!
About Women at work
Esme, from British duo Women at work, brings a vibrant and genre-defying experience to the dance floor, blending breaks, garage, jungle, and anything with bass. Based in Amsterdam, she has played at Sexyland World, Radio Radio, A&amp;rsquo;DAM tower, Operator Radio and more.</description></item><item><title>DJ Tracksuit</title><link>https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/radio_archive/2024_02_28/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/radio_archive/2024_02_28/</guid><description>February 28, 2024 / DJ Tracksuit (he/him) / 6-7PM Hour of Power - a show where I play music that I play in clubs. Usually around 128bpm.
About DJ Tracksuit
Find him on the dancefloor with his (self-proclaimed) great dance moves or in the booth, mixing records at listening bars and clubs all around Europe. DJ Tracksuit’s sound travels through the grooves and rhythms of the African diaspora, taking you to dizzying heights of Spiritual Jazz, heavy lows of Dub, Reggae and Deep House, then twists you into a joyous state with Zouk and Disco.</description></item><item><title>Boogie Mind</title><link>https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/radio_archive/2024_01_17/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.frontleftbythespeaker.nl/radio_archive/2024_01_17/</guid><description>Boogie Mind / January 17, 2024 / 6-8PM The show will take a focus on a spectrum of music I been exploring lately ranging between acid dub/ jungle and Tech.
About Boogie Mind Walid draws his passion from a deep well of musical influences. His journey into the realm of music began with his first love, Jazz. With his fusion of jazz, hip hop, and percussive influences, he weaves a tapestry of sonic landscapes that transports listeners to new realms of musical discovery.</description></item></channel></rss>